[{"answer": "my friend, it's", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "He's not there. Huggie Bear isn't in every single episode", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " What does my friend say", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "This is he", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "He says. This is he", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No. This is he", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "It's true, my friend", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " I'll just drive my car", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What was that all about", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What did I say", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I warned you, my friend", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, I was saying crazy like a lunatic", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I know that now. He's a fucking psycho", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I do blame you, my friend. And woah. Look at her", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Where's that guy going", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well, I left some money in there", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What's your name", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "How do you say nineteen", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Right. Yeah. Yo soy dies y nueve. How old are you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Were you born in that place", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh, really? That's interesting. Do you prefer that place or the that place", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I know it's not", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yes, I do", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend.  And this is my associate my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend, we're on the run from the law here. Did you tell these people your real name", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "They don't", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "And if Future Man doesn't get let out of jail in 48 hours, then we go back. All right", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "As long as he gets out OK", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "This morning", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You were asleep", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "He told you and you let him do it", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " If you wanted to go? What were you going to do? Just leave me here by myself", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I don't think we can do that", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "What I'm saying is she wouldn't go for that", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You can't just run home every time things get tough. First of all, we've got enough dough to", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " You're so spoiled. What is", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Sixty days", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Why were you drawing the Holy my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yeah. One minute you're studying Great Expectations and the next minute you're drawing the Holy my friend for some kid who tried to stab his girlfriend", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Prison tatoos. I got to be pretty good. It's not like drawing on paper", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What is it", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "What's Hinckley Cold Storage", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yeah. And I'll tell you who we're going to wan", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "He's damn good", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "He said what", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "No. I didn't run away. I went out of town", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, we'll see you later, my friend", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": " Nice to meet you", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Did my friend take the test", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "How'd he do", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I don't think you will", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Look, you're going to do fine. It's OK to be scared", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Do you like my friend", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Yeah. As a girl", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Yeah. As a girl", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "So do I", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Everything OK", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "It looks pretty good. There's nobody back here", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Who? Applejack", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "He's going to watch the back stairwell, remember?  Don't worry about it", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Where's my friend", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Jesus Christ, my friend.  Did you lose him", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": " What can I say? It's jail. You don't sleep when you want to. You don't eat when you want to", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "We don't have rooms, my friend. We have cells", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Do you have your own room", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Do you have your own cell", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "We don't have rooms, my friend. We have cells", "docId": "Bottle-Rocket.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "No. I have a cellmate. His name's my friend", "qsentId": 70}]